<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on INTELLIGENT DATA - INTENSIVE SYSTEMS</title>
    <link>https://id-is.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on INTELLIGENT DATA - INTENSIVE SYSTEMS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 22:16:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://id-is.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI4Copernicus</title>
      <link>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Reinforcing the AI4EU Platform by Advancing Earth Observation Intelligence, Innovation and Adoption
January 1, 2021 - December 31, 2023
 AI4Copernicus aims to make the AI4EU AI-on-demand platform the platform of choice for users of Copernicus data along the value chain (scientists, SMEs, non-tech sector). AI4Copernicus will achieve this by exposing AI4EU resources on DIAS (data and information access services) platforms, making it easy to procure computing power and large EO data, as well as to access training material and expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI4EU</title>
      <link>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-2/</guid>
      <description>A European AI On Demand Platform and Ecosystem
January 1, 2019 - December 31, 2021
 AI4EU will efficiently build a comprehensive European AI-on-demand platform to lower barriers to innovation, to boost technology transfer and catalyse the growth of start-ups and SMEs in all sectors through open calls and other actions. The platform will act as a broker, developer and one-stop shop providing and showcasing services, expertise, algorithms, software frameworks, development tools, components, modules, data, computing resources, prototyping functions and access to funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DARE</title>
      <link>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Delivering Agile Research Excellence on European e-Infrastructures
January 1, 2018 - December 31, 2020
 DARE aims to provide scientific communities with a unifying hyper-platform and development context to allow for user-friendly and reproducible carrying out of huge data-driven experiments, and rapid prototyping. DARE specifically addresses the requirements of innovating teams of research developers and scientists, who work on the intersection of software engineering and scientific domains, and on data, complexity and computing extremes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fair for Fusion</title>
      <link>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://id-is.github.io/projects/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Open access for fusion data in Europe
September 1, 2019 - August 31, 2021
 The European fusion community has become increasingly collaborative over the last few decades with more experimental devices becoming available for broader groups of researchers. The diversity of devices is a great strength of the programme, but as each facility largely has developed their own data technologies, philosophies and access methodologies it has in some cases also presented challenges in sharing data even between collaborating scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
